necklace1 =[
  {"question":"瑪蒂達","Answer":"mǎdì dá"},
  {"question":"丈夫","Answer":"zhàngfu"},
  {"question":"迷人","Answer":"mírén"},
  {"question":"貧窮","Answer":"pínqióng"},
  {"question":"教育部","Answer":"jiàoyùbù"},
  {"question":"基層","Answer":"jīcéng"},
  {"question":"職員","Answer":"zhíyuán"},
  {"question":"儉樸","Answer":"jiǎnpǔ"},
  {"question":"羨慕","Answer":"xiànmù"},
  {"question":"奢侈","Answer":"shēchǐ"},
  {"question":"適合","Answer":"shìhé"},
  {"question":"破舊","Answer":"pòjiù"},
  {"question":"宮廷","Answer":"gōngtíng"},
  {"question":"裝潢","Answer":"zhuānghuáng"},
  {"question":"豪","Answer":"háo"},
  {"question":"宅","Answer":"zhái"},
  {"question":"房子","Answer":"fángzi"},
  {"question":"美味","Answer":"měiwèi"},
  {"question":"丈夫","Answer":"zhàngfu"},
  {"question":"魯阿奇","Answer":"zhàngfu"},
  {"question":"共進","Answer":"gòngjìn"},
  {"question":"實在","Answer":"shízài"},
  {"question":"稱讚","Answer":"chēngzàn"},
  {"question":"無動於衷","Answer":"wúdòngyúzhōng"},
  {"question":"儉樸","Answer":"jiǎnpǔ"},
  {"question":"富麗堂皇","Answer":"fùlìtánghuáng"},
  {"question":"豪宅","Answer":"háozhái"},
  {"question":"名門","Answer":"míngmén"},
  {"question":"紳士","Answer":"shēnshì"},
  {"question":"川流不息","Answer":"chuānliúbùxī"},
  {"question":"享用","Answer":"xiǎngyòng"},
  {"question":"豪華","Answer":"háohuá"},
  {"question":"晚餐","Answer":"wǎncān"},
  {"question":"未","Answer":"wèi"},
  {"question":"鍾愛","Answer":"zhōngài"},
  {"question":"昂","Answer":"áng"},
  {"question":"貴","Answer":"guì"},
  {"question":"寶石","Answer":"bǎoshí"},
  {"question":"偏偏","Answer":"piānpiān"},
  {"question":"昂貴","Answer":"ángguì"},
  {"question":"拜訪","Answer":"bàifǎng"},
  {"question":"滋味","Answer":"zīwèi"},
  {"question":"傍晚","Answer":"bàngwǎn"},
  {"question":"愉悅","Answer":"yúyuè"},
  {"question":"逗","Answer":"dòu"},
  {"question":"專門","Answer":"zhuānmén"},
  {"question":"丈夫","Answer":"zhàngfu"},
  {"question":"信封","Answer":"xìnfēng"},
  {"question":"拆開","Answer":"chāikāi"},
  {"question":"部長","Answer":"bùzhǎng"},
  {"question":"宴會","Answer":"yànhuì"},
  {"question":"邀請函","Answer":"yāoqǐnghán"},
  {"question":"分","Answer":"fēn"},
  {"question":"代替","Answer":"dàitì"}
]